

Anton Cerneavschii

Unity Developer

Good day, My name is Anton and I'm a Unity game developer with over a 4 years experience.

I have experience in working with 2D, 3D development in a Unity, from hyper-casual to midcore.

Very self-motivated programmer with a great desire to develop and strive for the heights of the gaming industry.

I love math and physics, especially in the application with the gaming industry.

A very difficult relationship with sleep, because it has as many as 2 serious competitors – coffee and programming:)

Skills:

- 1. Android/IOS/PC development, Unity engineering.
- 2. Multiplayer development (Photon PUN, Fusion, Netcode for GameObject, Lobby, Relay).
- 3. Architectures and cores based on Zenject (and others DI containers).
- 4. Unity DOTS(ECS, Jobs, Burst)
- 5. Worked with unit testing.
- 6. Experience with working with asynchronous code, Jobs system.
- 7. Architect and creating custom packages.
- 8. Procedural mesh generation process and features.
- 9. Making Shaders knowledges using Shader Graph, understanding of render systems.
- 10. AR systems development experience.
- 11. C, C++, SFML, microprocessors development experience.

Work Experience

Unity Developer at Blue Gravity Studios

2022 - 2023

- Working with midcore projects, with full development cycle.
- Creating game architecture.
- Working with ECS, DI (Zenject).
- Development of ,ultiplayer core (based on NetCode for GameObjects)

Unity Developer at TryMyGames SRL

2021 - 2022

- 2D, 3D Unity development.
- Hyper casual games, casual games development.
- Game Creating full cycle management.
- Various plugins, assets for game development.
- Working with procedural meshes, splines, Zenject, ECS.
- Working with Shaders based on Shader Graph.

Unity Developer at Midnight Works

2020 - 2021

- 3D development in a Unity.
- Multiplayer based on Photon PUN.
- Hyper casual games android/iOS development.
- Casual games development.
- Procedural mesh generation, creating basic shaders, various. pluginsfor Unity, algorithms, many different assets.

Education History

Technical University of Moldova

Bachelor of Biomedical Engineering, 2023

Links and Contacts

Email: cherneavschii.anton@gmail.com

LinkedIn: LinkedIn Profile

Portfolio: Portfolio Link